ANGELA AHN

Product & UX Designer

www.angelaahn.com 909.477.7741 angelaashley@gmail.com

I have been designing digital products for 3+ years across different industries. My background in math inspires me to find patterns and seek consistency in design. Currently at MSC, I find myself designing 3D experiences and learning about mechanical engineering.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UX / UI Designer at MSC Software | Oct. 2017 - Present

- Working on a project supported by Honda to achieve multi-viewport functionality in the application
- Conducting surveys and regularly meeting with Honda to get feedback on the design and make adjustments
- Designing a tool to enhance Apex-Nastran interoperability for Boeing
- Managing internal UX/UI design documentation

UX Designer at Project Narnia | Mar. 2017 - Dec. 2017

- Designed a mobile application to increase communication between charities and donors
- Conducted user testing and interviews with stakeholders and refined the design iteratively based on user feedback

UX / UI Designer at Lending QB | Mar. 2016 - Sep. 2017

- Worked as the lead designer on the UI re-design project collaborating closely with developers and project managers within the agile workflow
- Created a living style guide inspired by Material Design Guidelines and designed the web application to be responsive
- Ran surveys and user testing sessions with stakeholders
- Created and managed the internal design documentation

Integration Product Designer at LendingOB | Dec. 2014 - Mar. 2016

- Designed web services to allow users with custom UI to interact with the application
- Designed data mappings between loan data from the application to XML payload

Faculty Advisor at Envision (Engineer & Tech.) | Jun. 2014 - Aug. 2014

English-Korean Interpreter at NWLS | Apr. 2014 - Jun. 2014

EDUCATION

Interaction Design Specialization at Coursera | Oct. 2018 - Present

UX Design at General Assembly | Nov. 2016 - Feb. 2017

Web Design (HTML / CSS) at UC Irvine Ext. | Sep. 2016 - Nov. 2016

Bachelor of Arts, Mathematics at UC Berkeley | Aug. 2009 - Dec. 2013

SKILLS

User Research
User Interview
Contextual Inquiry
Competitive Analysis
User Persona
User Flow
User Journey Map
High-Fidelity Wireframe
Rapid Prototype
User Testing

TOOLS

Figma Sketch InVision Adobe XD Adobe Illustrator HTML5/CSS3 Balsamiq Snagit Confluence JIRA Visual Paradigm

RECOGNITION

Competent Communicator at Toastmasters Int'l 1st Place Winner at Humorous Speech

Design Chair at Relay for Life

LANGUAGES

English Korean